[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "If I had known you were coming ___.",
    "options": [
      "I had gone to the station.",
      "I would have gone to the station.",
      "I would be going to the station.",
      "I would go to the station."
    ],
    "answer": "I would have gone to the station."
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Choose the correct option: Even as harvesting was goin on ___.",
    "options": [
      "the rainy season begins",
      "the rainy season had began",
      "the rainy season was began",
      "the rainy season began"
    ],
    "answer": "the rainy season began"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which phrase contains words opposed to each other in meaning?",
    "options": [
      "Reproduction and death",
      "Heat and dust",
      "Hopes and aspirations",
      "Emerged and advanced"
    ],
    "answer": "Reproduction and death"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Find out the correct translation: সকাল থেকে গুঁড়ি গুঁড়ি বৃষ্টি হচ্ছে।",
    "options": [
      "It is raining from morning.",
      "It has been raining from morning.",
      "It has been drizzling since morning.",
      "It is drizzling since morning."
    ],
    "answer": "It has been drizzling since morning."
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Maiden speech means-",
    "options": ["First speech", "Last speech", "Late speech", "Early speech"],
    "answer": "First speech"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "A person whose 'head' is in the 'clouds' is-----",
    "options": ["an aviator", "proud", "a day dreamer", "useless"],
    "answer": "a day dreamer"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Identify the correct sentence:",
    "options": [
      "She had faith and hopes in future.",
      "She had faith and hopes in the future.",
      "She had faith and hopes for the future.",
      "She had faith in and hopes for the future."
    ],
    "answer": "She had faith in and hopes for the future."
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Choose the correct tense:",
    "options": [
      "Javed was so exhausted that he was lying down for a sleep",
      "Javed was so exhausted that he had lain down for a sleep",
      "Javed was so exhausted that he will lay down for a sleep",
      "Javed was so exhausted that he lain down for a sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "Javed was so exhausted that he was lying down for a sleep"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "A synonym for 'resentment' is-",
    "options": ["fear", "anger", "indignation", "panic"],
    "answer": "anger"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "The captain left the boat, because it ___.",
    "options": ["turned over", "tuned bottom", "turned up", "turned down"],
    "answer": "turned over"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "One should be careful about ___ duty.",
    "options": ["her", "one’s", "His", "the"],
    "answer": "one’s"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Three-fourths of the work __ finished.",
    "options": ["have been", "has been", "had", "were"],
    "answer": "has been"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "We waited until the plane ___.",
    "options": [
      "had taken off",
      "had not taken off",
      "took off",
      "did not take off"
    ],
    "answer": "took off"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "I spent - -with the patient.",
    "options": ["Sometimes", "sometime", "some times", "some time"],
    "answer": "some time"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence:",
    "options": [
      "Rahim ate the whole fish almost",
      "Almost Rahim ate the whole fish",
      "Rahim ate almost the whole fish",
      "Rahim almost ate the whole fish"
    ],
    "answer": "Rahim ate almost the whole fish"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "She argued ___ me about the marriage.",
    "options": ["with", "From", "for", "to"],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "I count - -your help.",
    "options": ["with", "After", "upon", "for"],
    "answer": "upon"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Identify the correct passive form-'Open the window'",
    "options": [
      "Let the window be opened",
      "The window should be opened",
      "Let the window be opened by you",
      "The window must be opened"
    ],
    "answer": "Let the window be opened"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "The appropriate meaning of the idiom 'Swan song' -----",
    "options": ["first work", "last work", "middle work", "early work"],
    "answer": "last work"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Trees have - - off their leaves",
    "options": ["fallen", "cast", "Thrown", "put"],
    "answer": "cast"
  }
]
